♪♪
♪ Hey, I, I ♪
♪ Yeah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Yeah, I ♪
♪ An old man turned ninety-eight ♪
♪ He won the lottery ♪
♪ and died the next day ♪
♪ It's a black fly
in your Chardonnay ♪
♪ It's death row pardon ♪
♪ two minutes too late ♪
♪ And isn't it ironic... ♪
♪ don't you think ♪
♪ It's like rain ♪
♪ on your wedding day ♪
♪ It's free a ride ♪
♪ when you've already paid ♪
♪ It's the good advice
that you just didn't take ♪
♪ And who would've
thought...it figures ♪
♪ Mr. Play It Safe,
was afraid to fly ♪
♪ He packed his suitcase ♪
♪ and kissed his kids good-bye ♪
♪ He waited his
whole damn life ♪
♪ to take that flight ♪
♪ And as the plane
crashed down he thought ♪
♪ "Well isn't this nice..." ♪
♪ And isn't it ironic... ♪
♪ don't you think ♪
♪ It's like rain ♪
♪ on your wedding day ♪
♪ It's a free ride ♪
♪ when you've already paid ♪
♪ It's the good advice
that you just didn't take ♪
♪ And who would've
thought...it figures ♪
♪ Life has a funny way ♪
♪ of sneaking up on you when
you think everything's okay ♪
♪ and everything's going right ♪
♪ And life has a funny way ♪
♪ of helping you out when you
think everything's gone wrong ♪
♪ and everything blows
up in your face ♪
♪ A traffic jam when
you're already late ♪
♪ A no smoking sign on
your cigarette break ♪
♪ It's like 10,000 spoons
when all ya need is a knife ♪
♪ It's meeting the
man of my dreams ♪
♪ And then meeting
his beautiful wife ♪
♪ And isn't it ironic... ♪
♪ don't you think ♪
♪ A little too ironic... ♪
♪ and yeah, I really do think ♪
♪ It's like rain on
your wedding day ♪
♪ It's a free ride ♪
♪ when you've already paid ♪
♪ It's the good advice
that you just didn't take ♪
♪ And who would've
thought, it figures ♪
♪ And yeah, life
has a funny way ♪
♪ of sneaking up on you ♪
♪ And life has a
funny, funny way ♪
♪ of helping you out ♪
♪ Helping you out ♪
[ROLLING ON GRAVEL]
[RUSHING WIND]